http://www.wesleymc.org/privacy

Privacy Policy
Home
Privacy
Privacy Policy and Consent to Use of Personal Data
By interacting with, submitting information to or signing up for any organised activity offered by Wesley Methodist Church, you agree and consent to Wesley Methodist Church collecting, using, disclosing and sharing of your personal data, for the purpose of engagement, operational planning of activities, as well as communication of events, programmes and church-related information. You also agree that any information or data submitted to Wesley Methodist Church has been voluntarily provided and that it is reasonable to voluntarily provide such data or information. Wesley Methodist Church respects personal data and privacy, and will only share such information with third parties on a required basis. Should you wish to withdraw or limit your consent, please write with full particulars to our Data Protection Officer.
Wesley Methodist Church5 Fort Canning RoadSingapore 179493Tel: 6336 1433Email : This email address is being protected from spambots. You need JavaScript enabled to view it.
Next
HomeAbout UsChurch DirectionsThe Christian FaithBeliefs / MissionOur LeadersOur TeamOur HistoryThe Methodist Church in SingaporeContact UsPlan A VisitWelcomeWorship ServicesChildrenTweens (11-13 years old)YouthSeniorsDeaf and Hard-of-HearingGetting to WesleyMedia CentresGet InvolvedBaptism & MembershipJoin a Small GroupJoin a Missions TeamFellowship & Interest Groupse-Giving
Tithes (Pledges) and OfferingsJoin Us On StaffCarePray For MeCounsellingCancer Support GroupHomebound Visitation Hospital VisitationBereavementSpecial NeedsFinancial AssistanceGetting MarriedRegister A NewbornMembers Information UpdateOur MinistriesWorshipWorship and MusicPrayer and PraiseFilipino FellowshipMandarinPrayerCareCounsellingPastoral CareDiscipleshipSmall GroupsBaptism & MembershipDiscipleship & NurtureOutreachGirls' BrigadeChristian Outreach & Social ConcernsCrisis Relief Wesley (CRW)MissionsWitness & EvangelismLifestageCampusChildrenBeTweenYouthSeniorsFamily LifeOrganisationsWomen's Society of Christian ServiceCOVID-19Updates and AdvisoryJob Opportunities
© 2020 Wesley Methodist Church
